predictify.com 2009-05-02

# Privacy - Predictify

Predictify is committed to honoring the privacy of our users. Our privacy philosophy is based on a single core principle: we will not collect, use, or share any personally identifiable information about you without your knowledge. The following document outlines our privacy policy, which is incorporated by reference into our Terms of Use.

### When We Collect Information

#### Site Visits

When you visit our site, we may send one or more cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser. Cookies allow us to store user preferences and track trends in site usage in order to improve the quality of the user experience. Some Predictify features and services may not function properly when cookies are disabled.

When you use Predictify services, our servers automatically record information provided by your browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies.

#### Account Creation

When you create an account, we collect personal information, such as your name and email address, during the registration process. By default, some of this information will be visible to other users who view your profile. You may choose to make private one or more of these fields by updating your preferences on your account page.

#### Question Submission

To submit a question, you must log in to your account (you may not submit questions anonymously). Questions may be reviewed prior to being posted and are subject to our Question Guidelines.

#### Prediction Submission

Predictions you submit are included in the aggregated question results and stored in your account. By default, your prediction history will be visible to other users who view your profile. You may choose to hide your prediction history by updating your preferences on your account page.

Submitting a prediction may require that you provide demographic profile information that has been specifically requested by the question-asker, such as political affiliation or marital status. This information will be included in the question results but will not be linked to you or your account in a personally identifiable way. That is, question results may reflect that married respondents, in aggregate, predicted a different outcome than unmarried respondents, but not your specific response. Demographic information submitted with predictions will be added to your profile, where you can view it, change it, and/or delete it. To ensure that the information is current, we may ask you to update it from time to time. You may request that demographic information not be added to your profile by opting out on your account page.

#### Billing and Payments

When you submit a sponsored question, you are required to provide billing information, including a credit card number and billing address. When you withdraw your account balance from sponsored question payouts, you are required to provide payment information, including a mailing address (for payment by check) or a PayPal account number (for electronic payment). All financial information will be stored securely and will not be shared with any third party.

#### Communications

When you communicate with Predictify via email or phone, we may store copies of this correspondence for our records and to improve the quality of our services.

### When We Use Information

#### Question Results

On each question, we aggregate and display user predictions in various formats (maps, charts, etc.), including aggregated demographic information where available. Question results are publicly visible to all site visitors.

#### Prediction Scoring

Unlike a poll, we score every prediction you make against the actual outcome and notify you of your performance via email. You may opt out of email notifications by updating your preferences on your account page.

#### Internal Analysis

From time to time, we may conduct an analysis of data stored on our servers for the purposes of improving existing services or developing new products. We restrict such access to employees, contractors, and agents who are bound by confidentiality obligations and subject to discipline for their violation.

### When We Share Information

We may share aggregated, non-personal information with third parties, such as the number of total site visits or the results of a question. However, we will not share your personal information with third parties, except in the following limited circumstances:

1) With our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other trusted businesses or persons under the condition that they comply with this privacy policy.

2) When we have good faith reason to believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, or (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

In the case of a merger, acquisition, sale of assets, or bankruptcy, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### Data Security

We have established reasonable physical and technological security measures to protect against unauthorized access to, and use of, data collected on our site and stored on our servers. We cannot, however, guarantee the security of any information you transmit to Predictify, and you do so at your own risk.

Our site is hosted on servers located in the United States and is subject U.S. laws and regulations.

### Other Considerations

We may update this policy from time to time and post new versions on this page - please see the date of last revision to identify whether the policy has changed recently. In case of major revisions, we will prominently delineate those changes and post notification elsewhere on the site.

For more information about Predictify or our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@predictify.com](mailto:info@predictify).

#### Date of Last Revision: March 25, 2009
